[
    {
        "QNum": "1",
        "Question": "1+2?",
        "Opt1": "12",
        "Opt2": "1",
        "Opt3": "2",
        "Opt4": "3",
        "Ans": "3",
        "corr":""
    },
    {
        "QNum": "2",
        "Question": "3+4?",
        "Opt1": "1",
        "Opt2": "7",
        "Opt3": "42",
        "Opt4": "2",
        "Ans": "7",
        "corr":""
    },
    {
        "QNum": "3",
        "Question": "5+6?",
        "Opt1": "68",
        "Opt2": "45",
        "Opt3": "11",
        "Opt4": "3",
        "Ans": "11",
        "corr":""
    },
    {
        "QNum": "4",
        "Question": "7+8?",
        "Opt1": "1",
        "Opt2": "15",
        "Opt3": "4",
        "Opt4": "2",
        "Ans": "15",
        "corr":""
    },
    {
        "QNum": "5",
        "Question": "9+10?",
        "Opt1": "19",
        "Opt2": "32",
        "Opt3": "76",
        "Opt4": "2",
        "Ans": "19",
        "corr":""
    },
    {
        "QNum": "6",
        "Question": "11+12?",
        "Opt1": "5",
        "Opt2": "23",
        "Opt3": "85",
        "Opt4": "2",
        "Ans": "23",
        "corr":""
    },
    {
        "QNum": "7",
        "Question": "13+14?",
        "Opt1": "12",
        "Opt2": "27",
        "Opt3": "42",
        "Opt4": "64",
        "Ans": "27",
        "corr":""
    },
    {
        "QNum": "8",
        "Question": "15+16?",
        "Opt1": "75",
        "Opt2": "6",
        "Opt3": "34",
        "Opt4": "31",
        "Ans": "31",
        "corr":""
    },
    {
        "QNum": "9",
        "Question": "17+18?",
        "Opt1": "63",
        "Opt2": "44",
        "Opt3": "66",
        "Opt4": "35",
        "Ans": "35",
        "corr":""
    },
    {
        "QNum": "10",
        "Question": "19+20?",
        "Opt1": "2",
        "Opt2": "39",
        "Opt3": "1",
        "Opt4": "74",
        "Ans": "39",
        "corr":""
    }
]